B-CASカードを 不正に改ざんしたり
Return... Sasuke... to us...!
売ったりするのは 違法です。
絶対だめ！
He doesn't belong to you...
改ざんされたB-CASカードや
違法なチューナーは
Don't talk about Sasuke
in front of me,
使っちゃだめ！
like he belongs to you!
これからも
ちゃんと みてくださいね。
You are my friend.
you are my friend
Ah that day's dream...
aa ano hi no yume
You haven't forgotten it, have you?
ima demo mada wasuretenain deshou
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah it had just started your one longest way.
aa hajimatta bakka kimi no one longest way
サスケを… 返せ！
Woah, I'm starting on a journey now!
woah ima tabidatsu yo
EVERDAY hereafter is a shining day.
everyday kono saki mo shining day
ぐあ～っ！
Unchanging singin', a bright morning smile.
kawarazu singin' hikaru asa no smile
This is the last farewell on funny days.
kore de miosame no funny days
テメエのもんじゃねえ！
オレの前で 自分のものみてえに
サスケの名を口にするんじゃねえ！
Leaping into the future I see. Go far, dream of my heart.
tobidatsu future mezashita go far kokoro no dream of
I'll go the distance, the endless sky is blue.
i'll go the distance mihatenu sora wa blue
I've hitched a ride on the star ship, this is the best forever trip.
norikonda star ship kore ga saigo no forever trip
You are my friend.
you are my friend
Ah that day's dream...
aa ano hi no yume
You haven't forotten it, have you?
ima demo mada wasuretenai deshou
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah, it had just started your one longest way.
aa hajimatta bakka kimi no one longest way
Woah, I'm starting on a journey now!
woah ima tabidatsu yo
Thank you my friend.
thank you my friend
Ah even now,
aa ano hi no koto
I still remember that day.
ima demo mada oboeteru kara
You are my dream.
you are my dream
Ah those days that will never come back.
aa mou nidoto sou modoranai days
Woah I'll go the distance!
woah i'll go the distance
ぐっ…！
おもしろい…。
Interesting...
The Top-Secret
Mission Begins
《チャクラだけで…
チャクラだけで ここまで…》
With Chakra alone...
With Chakra alone,
he caused this much damage...
サクラ…！
Sakura!
《なんて チャクラだ…。
What incredible Chakra...
それに １人 勝手に暴走するとは。
Beyond that, it's going out of control,
like it has a will of its own...
But this is
the perfect opportunity...
だが これは絶好のチャンス。
いよいよ ここからが
極秘任務のスタートだ…》
Finally, the top-secret mission starts.
Sakura! Answer me!
(ヤマト)サクラ！ 返事をしろ！
《ヤマト : さっき倒れたときに
頭を打ったのか。
Did she hit her head
when she fell just now?
こんなときに気絶なんて…》
Passing out
at a time like this...!
木遁の術。
Wood Style Ninjutsu!
くっ…。
I can't support it...!
《支えきれない…》
Ninja Art: Super Beast Scroll!
(サイ)忍法 超獣偽画。
サイ！
Sai!
サイ！ サクラを！
Sai! Help Sakura...
Damn!
ったく…。
ふぅ…。
I see...
なるほどねぇ…。
人柱力の力を借りて その程度…。
You borrow
the power of the Jinchuriki...
And yet, that's
the best you can do...
ううぅ…。
You're still no match for Sasuke-kun...
まだまだ… サスケ君以下ね。
ううぅ…。
ぐっ…。
あぁっ…。
クア～ッ…。
う…。
何だってばよ ここ…。
What is... this place...?
(うなり声)
ん？
サスケ…。
Sasuke...?
サスケ！
Sasuke!
待てって！
Wait...
待ってくれ！
Wait for me...!
サスケ！
Sasuke...
《クッソ！》
Damn it...!
《オレには
サスケを連れ戻す 力がねえ》
I don't have... the power
to bring Sasuke back...
《あのとき… あのとき
オレがもっと強かったら…》
That time... back then...
if only I had been stronger...
((サスケ！ お前は 大蛇丸
なんかには やらねえってばよ！
Sasuke!
I won't let Orochimaru take you.
オレが お前の手足の骨
全部 折ってでも➡
I'll stop you even if...
I have to break every bone
in your arms and legs!
止めてやらあ！
(サスケ)お前は オレの額に傷ひとつ
つけることすら できやしない。
You can't even put
a scratch on my forehead.
そのことに 変わりはないがな。
That much has not changed.
う～っ！
でも しようがねえよな。
It's hopeless, I tell you...
ナルト…。
Naruto...
確かに お前は特別だった。
you were a special one...
だがな オレは お前以上に特別だ。
but...
I am even more special than you!
千鳥！
Chidori!
螺旋丸！
Rasengan!
(千鳥！
螺旋丸！))
- Chidori!
- Rasengan!
《オレが弱えから
オレの言葉は ヤツに届かねえ。
I am weak, so my words
don't reach him...
オレが弱えから
ヤツは オレを認めねえ》
Because I am weak,
I can't win his recognition...
《だから… なにがなんでも
強くならなきゃならねえ》
So... whatever happens,
I must become stronger...
《やっとできた つながりを➡
So that the bond I've finally forged
will not be severed...
断ち切られないように…》
《サスケに オレとの繋がりを
断ち切らせないために！》
So that Sasuke won't sever
the connection between me...!
SEAL
どりゃ～っ！
この感じ 今までと違うわね。
This feeling... it's different
from before, isn't it...?
(ヤマト)サクラ しっかりしろ！
おい サクラ!!
Sakura, snap out of it!
Hey, Sakura!
大丈夫か？
Are you all right?
はい…。
Y-Yes...
おい！
(サクラ)すみません。
Hey...!
Sorry...
もう 大丈夫です。
I'm okay now...
(サクラ)これって…。
(ヤマト)ナルトがやったのさ。
What happened here...?
Naruto did it...
ふぅ…。
人柱力の力…。
The Jinchuriki...
ヤツらが欲しがるのも無理ないね。
It only stands to reason
that they'd want it too...
ナルトは？
橋の向こう側だよ。
Where's Naruto now?!
On the other side of the bridge...
with Orochimaru.
大蛇丸と一緒にね。
《やっかいなのは ナルトだな》
Naruto is a real handful...
あの煙は…。
What's that smoke...?
I have a bad feeling about this...
《イヤな予感がする…》
Wood Clone Jutsu!
木分身の術！
頼むぞ！
うむ。
I'm counting on you!
Right.
ぐおぉ…。
はっ！
ぐおぉぉ!!
木遁 木錠壁！
Wood Style: Doomed Wall!
Naruto...!
《ナルト…》
Simply unbelievable,
おもしろいじゃない…。
まったく この子は…。
the things this child can do...
(ヤマト)しまった…。
Oh shoot...
Reach for it, reach for it, far away.
todoke todoke tooku e
Now I trust these revived tears to you.
ima wo kishikaisei namida azukete
It begins.
hajimare
A long, long story about you
nagai nagai kimi monogatari
"Tears", "tears".
namidatte namidatte
I want to shed them in happy times
ureshii toki ni nagashitai
So what if I want them to float in pretty puddles?
kirei na mizutamari ukabetai no wa nani
The southern sky,
minami no sora ni
It twinkles.
matataiteiru
From all of the stars meeting.
hoshi no kazu hodo no deai kara
Learning about love, receiving a map.
ai wo manandari chizu wo morattari
Are connected.
tsunagatteku
Reach for it, reach for it, far away.
todoke todoke tooku e
木ノ葉 青春エクササイズ！
Now I trust these revived tears to you.
ima wo kishikaisei namida azukete
今回は オレたち忍の
修業を紹介するぜ！
まずは ステップ ワン！
体力づくり！
Someday a new page will turn.
itsuka mekuru peeji ni
忍にとって
最も大事な 基礎体力。
I'm sure it'll be filled with lots of people
kitto takusan no hito ga afureru
(サクラ)修業の方法は
人 それぞれ。
逆立ち 指立て伏せ。
It begins,
hajimare
崖登り。 逆立ちして 里を１周。
A long, long story about you.
nagai nagai kimi monogatari
って どれも 汗くさいわね。
ステップ ツー！
木登り。
Next Episode
チャクラを足の裏に集めて
維持するのがポイントだってばよ。
Damn it!
He unleashed a shock wave
of that magnitude...
simply by swinging
one of his arms down. Good grief!
ステップ スリー！
Is that Naruto's
Nine-Tailed power?
(サクラ)足にためたチャクラを
一定量 放出しながら➡
Yes, it is.
体重のバランスをとるのが コツ。
Please tell me, Captain Yamato.
You know something
about Naruto, don't you?
じゃないと ドッボ～ン！
Sakura...
こうして見ると ムチャしてるわね。
What on earth
will become of Naruto?
He'll be fine.
You don't have to worry.
でも これらは
日々の訓練のたまものだから➡
It was for just such times as this
that I was chosen as Team Captain.
テレビの前のみんなは…。
一緒に 火影を目指して➡
レッツ 修業！
(サクラ)できるかっ！
Orochimaru vs Jinchuriki
Next time: "Orochimaru vs Jinchuriki"
危険だから
絶対にマネしないでね。
Training of Leaf Ninja.
Today we'll introduce our shinobi training!
First, Step One!
Building physical strength!
The most important thing to a shinobi
is basic physical strength.
Training methods vary
from person to person.
There's the thumb-stand push-up,
also cliff climbing,
and the handstand
tour of the village!
Say, they all leave you
smelling sweaty, don't they?
Step Two!
Tree Climbing!
The main point is to
gather all your chakra
in the soles of your feet
and maintain it.
Step Three!
The key is to balance
your body weight
while releasing a certain amount
of chakra!
If you don't...
Splash!
Looking back at it like this, we sure
train in a reckless way don't we?
But these are results from
our daily training.
So everyone who's
watching this TV...
Let's train together
to become Hokage!
Like heck they can!
It's dangerous so
never try this at home, ok?